Guide to the Chaplain's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Chaplain's Office records, 1985-2005; Accession 2007-A-220
  - Yale Religious Ministry (YRM) Notes
    - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Covenants, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Address Book, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Covenant, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Minutes, Agenda, Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - YRM, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Church of Christ at Yale Council (CCY)
    - Staff Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Social Action, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Church Pledges, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Directory, circa 1994 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Council notes, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 94 - 96)
    - Pastoral Search Committee, Circa 1998 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Church Council Minutes, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Core Group, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Annual Reports
    - 1985-1990, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - 1996 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 105 - 106)
  - Annual Budget
    - 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Pledge Information
    - 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 111 - 112)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 115 - 116)
    - Acknowledgment Letters, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Annual meeting, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Student Papers for Spring 2004 Class
    - Chasing Grace, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Memory Slips, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - All But My Life, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Do They Hear You When You Cry, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Paula, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Food and Loathing, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Daybook, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Zami, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Expecting Adam, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Practicing Resurrection, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Miriam's Kitchen, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Student Papers for Spring 2004 class "Women's Spiritual Autobiography" outlines and notes (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Final Papers, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 131 - 133)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence
    - Memos, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 134 - 135)
    - Jerry's Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 136 - 137)
    - Chaplain's Office Correspondence, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Inter-University Correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box 5, Folder 139 - 140)
    - Miscellaneous Letters-Jerry, 1991-2001 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Fall, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Jerry's Letters, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 143 - 145)
    - Summer, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - Correspondence (Reverend Streets), 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 147 - 149)
    - Installation, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Installation Names and Addresses, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Installation of Jerry Streets, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Correspondence, Rev. Streets
    - Yale Memos, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - 1994 (Box 6, Folder 154 - 156)
    - 1995 (Box 6, Folder 157 - 159)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - 1996 (Box 6, Folder 161)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 162 - 163)
    - 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 164)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 165)
    - Miscellaneous Letters to Jerry, 1993-2000 (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - Interoffice correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - Tercentennial and FPC 2004
    - 2004 FPC Info (Box 6A, Folder 168)
    - Lois Palav Chapel Event, 2001 (Box 6A, Folder 169)
    - Tapes Audio/Video Orders, 2001-2002 (Box 6A, Folder 171)
    - Preaching Series, 1998-2002 (Box 6A, Folder 172)
    - Bio and Pictures, 2000-2001 (Box 6A, Folder 173)
    - Program, 1999 (Box 6A, Folder 174)
    - Publicity, 2001 (Box 6A, Folder 175)
    - Misc, 2001 (Box 6A, Folder 176)
    - Travel and Hotel, 2001 (Box 6A, Folder 177)
    - Follow Up, 2001 (Box 6A, Folder 178)
    - Original Sermons, 2001 (Box 6A, Folder 179)
    - Correspondence (Reverend Streets), 2001 (Box 6A, Folder 180)
    - Last Semester, 2001 (Box 6A, Folder 181)
    - Contact Info, 2000-2001 (Box 6A, Folder 182)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, meeting agendas, and other documents, 1989-1999 (Box 6A, Folder 183A)
  - Bulletins
    - 1987
      - January-May (Box 7, Folder 184 - 188)
      - August-December (Box 7, Folder 189 - 193)
      - Special Services (Box 7, Folder 194)
    - 1988
      - January-June (Box 7, Folder 195 - 200)
      - September-December (Box 7, Folder 201 - 204)
      - Special Services (Box 7, Folder 205)
    - 1989
      - January-June (Box 7, Folder 206 - 211)
      - September-December (Box 7, Folder 212 - 215)
      - Special Services (Box 7, Folder 216)
    - 1990
      - January-June (Box 7, Folder 217 - 222)
      - September-December (Box 7, Folder 223 - 226)
      - Special Services (Box 7, Folder 227)
    - 1991
      - January-June (Box 7, Folder 228 - 233)
      - September-December (Box 7, Folder 234 - 237)
    - 1992
      - January-June (Box 8, Folder 238 - 243)
      - August-December (Box 8, Folder 244 - 248)
      - Special Services (Box 8, Folder 249)
    - 1993
      - January-June (Box 8, Folder 250 - 255)
      - August-December (Box 8, Folder 256 - 260)
      - Special Services (Box 8, Folder 261)
    - 1994
      - January-December (Box 8, Folder 262 - 273)
      - Special Services (Box 8, Folder 274)
    - 1995
      - January-June (Box 8, Folder 275 - 280)
      - August-December (Box 8, Folder 281 - 285)
      - Special Services (Box 8, Folder 286)
    - 1996 January - December (Box 8, Folder 287 - 298)
    - 1997
      - January-December (Box 9, Folder 299 - 310)
      - Special Services (Box 9, Folder 311)
    - 1998 January - December (Box 9, Folder 312 - 323)
    - 1999 January-November (Box 9, Folder 324 - 334)
    - 2000
      - January-June (Box 9, Folder 335 - 340)
      - October-December (Box 9, Folder 341 - 343)
    - 2001 January-December (Box 9, Folder 344 - 355)
    - 2002 January-December (Box 10, Folder 356 - 367)
    - 2003 January-December (Box 10, Folder 368 - 379)
    - 2004 January-December (Box 10, Folder 380 - 391)
    - 2005 January-December (Box 10, Folder 392 - 403)
  - Newsletters
    - 1989-1994 (Box 11, Folder 404 - 408)
    - 1994-1997 (Box 12, Folder 409 - 411)
    - 1999 (Box 12, Folder 412)
- Chaplain's Office records, 1950-2007; Accession 2009-A-130
  Materials in boxes 1-6 are restricted until January 1, 2043 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.; boxes 7-11 are open for research.
  - Administrative
    Materials are restricted until January 1, 2043 due to University policy.
    - Alcoholism/[name redacted], 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Annual reports
    - CCY Annual Reports, 1999-2005 (Box 1, Folder 16 - 21)
  - Meetings and Newsletters
    - CCY Council Meetings, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 22 - 24)
    - CCY Staffing Minutes, 1999-2004 (Box 2, Folder 25 - 30)
    - Battell Articles etc., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - In Care Status
  - CCY Membership Newsletters
    - Confidential Resignation NRL, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Church Directory and information, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 38 - 39)
  - Newsletters
    - Battell Newsletter, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 40 - 44)
  - Special Bulletins and Remembrance Materials
    - Lenten Booklet, 1999, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 45 - 46)
    - All Saints Day, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Good Friday, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Maundy Thursday, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Holy Week Services, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Services of Remembrance, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Administrative
    - Ocha, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Memorial Services, 1994-2000 (Box 2, Folder 53 - 56)
    - Jerry's Speaking Schedule, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Hardship Program, Refugee Trauma, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Harvard Program for Refugee Trauma, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Bosnia, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Frustrated Fellowship, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - The Greenhoe Lectures, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Albert Schweitzer Institute, Bishop Tutu, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - General to Student Organizations, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Governor's Ethnic Committee, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Daughters of Rizpah, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Faith Matters, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Living By the Word/Christian Century, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - COUSAC, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Articles
      - New York Times, 2002-2006 (Box 3, Folder 71 - 81)
      - Yale Daily News, 2002-2006 (Box 3, Folder 82 - 104)
      - Yale Bulletin and Calendar, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 105)
      - Yale Divinity, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 106)
      - Yale Alumni Magazine, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 107)
      - New Haven Register, 2002-2006 (Box 3, Folder 108 - 116)
      - Hartford Courant, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 117 - 118)
      - Living Pulpit, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 119 - 120)
    - Press Releases, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 121 - 122)
    - Pomp, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Welcoming New Members, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Tercentennial, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 125 - 127)
  - Copyrights, Approvals, Notes
    - University Church / Battell ceremonies: weddings, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Battell Video Podcasting Speaker Approval, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Pitney Bowes, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Weekly worship notes, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Sunday Evening Bulletins, 2006 September-November (Box 3, Folder 132 - 134)
    - Lent, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Consultant Task Force, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Job Description - Pastoral Assistant, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Membership, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Copyrights, 1994-2004 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Miscellaneous letters, 1993-2006 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Church of Christ at Yale Council
    - Baptismal Certificate - CCY, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - CCY Council Ordination Papers, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - CCY Reader's Suggestions and Usher Guidelines, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - CCY Meeting Records, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - CCY Organizational Development, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - CCY in Yale, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - CCY - Constitution and Bylaws, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - CCY letters of transfer, 1993-2004 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - CCY Pastor's Compensation Guidelines, 1994-1999 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - CCY - Our Covenant for Working Together, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Pamela bro Contract, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Battell: Open, Affirming, and Accessible, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Services, 9/11, Holy Week
    - Lessons and Carols, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - June Second, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Music Silence and Light, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 156 - 157)
    - 9/11 Events, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Ash Wednesday, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Good Friday, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Reunion, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Academic Guest Seminars, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Midterm Survival Kit, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Reunion, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Holy Week, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Lenten Noontime Bulletins, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Reunion Bulletins, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Advent Reflections, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Ash Wednesday, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Goddard Memorial, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Stations of the Cross, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Summary of Activities, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Desk Calendar and Plan Book, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Service of Remembrance, 1999-2006 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Holy Week, 2001-2004 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - FPC, Service of Remembrance 1960s, New Members
    - FPC, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 176 - 179)
    - McGuire Fund, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Music-Battel, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Entering UCC, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Service of Remembrance, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Rededication of Battell, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - In-care, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - New Members, 1994-2000 (Box 4, Folder 186 - 192)
    - Pamphlets/Publicity, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Prayers Battell, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Social Action and Newsletter, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Stewardship, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Undergraduates, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - YRM, 1960-2000 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Council Retreat, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Womentalk, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Committees, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - New Haven Bus Service, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Conscientious Objectors, 1967-1991 (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Annual Reports, Sermons and Prayers
    - CCY Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Preachers/Services, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Individual Sermons, 1987-1998 (Box 5, Folder 207 - 215)
    - Sermons and Prayers, 1989-1995 (Box 5, Folder 216 - 221)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 222)
  - Finances
    - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Annual Report, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 225)
  - Sermons and Worship Notes
    - Sermons- Vannorsdall, 1976-1985 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Sermons-Schaper et al, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Audrey Kerr Sermon, 2003 July 27 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Guest Speakers, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Wesley Arram, 2004 April 18 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Leon Burrows, 2000 November 12 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Rabbi Herbert Brockman, 2000 September 17 (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Davida Foy Crabtree, 1999 November 17 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Marian W. Edelman, 1999 October 10 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Martha C. Highsmith, 2005 April 17 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Sidney Lovett, Jr., 1985 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Barbara K. Lunblad, 2000 October 8 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Peter Gomes, 1998 October 11 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Martin Montonye, 2000 August 13 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Reverend Allie Perry, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Cynthie Terry's Sermons, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - Harold C. Waurlick, Jr., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - Sermons, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - Newsletters and Pastoral Notes, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 246)
    - Worship Notes, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 247)
    - Common Quest, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - WCRP/Wellsley Interreligious Campus Stuff, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - Certificates of Marriage and Baptism, 1967-1995 (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - AIDS Memorial Quilt, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - Chaplains Office Events, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 252)
    - Supervised Ministry application papers, 1995-2004 (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - Church, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 254)
    - Children's Choir Music, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 255)
    - Christmas Pageant, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - Battell Ushers, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 257)
    - Battell Deacons, 1957-1978 (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - Hillel AJWS, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 259)
    - Copyright License, 2002-2007 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - Rev. David Hinson, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - MTI Children of Eden, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - Donations to Battel, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Sermon Lending Library, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Carisa Feria, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - Builders of a Brighter Cambodia, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - Body Image Awareness Week, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - Closing + Codes, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Gilbert Levine, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Religious and Spiritual Life at Yale, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 271)
    - Staff Meeting- Opening Session 5, 2000-2007 (Box 6, Folder 272)
  - Miscellaneous
    - DelMar College, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - Event File, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 274)
    - Partnership of Ministry and Medicinr: Hope in Urban America, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 275)
  - University Public Worship Bulletins
    - 1950 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - 1951 (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - 1952 (Box 7, Folder 278)
    - 1953 (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - 1954 (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - 1955 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - 1956 (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - 1957 (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - 1958 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - 1959 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - 1960 Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - 1960 Jul-Dec (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - 1961 Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - 1961 Jul-Dec (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - 1962 Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - 1962 Jul-Dec (Box 7, Folder 291)
    - 1963 Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - 1963 Jul-Dec (Box 7, Folder 293)
    - 1964 Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 294)
    - 1964 Jul-Dec (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 7, Folder 297)
    - 1966 Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - 1966 Jul-Dec (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - 1967 Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - 1967 Jul-Dec (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - 1968 Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - 1968 Jul-Dec (Box 7, Folder 303)
    - 1969 Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - 1969 Jul-Dec (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - 1970 Jan (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - 1970 Feb (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - 1970 Mar (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - 1970 Apr (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - 1970 May (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - 1970 Sep (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - 1970 Oct (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - 1970 Nov (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - 1970 Dec (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - 1971 Jan (Box 7, Folder 315)
    - 1971 Feb (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - 1971 Mar (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - 1971 Apr (Box 7, Folder 318)
    - 1971 May (Box 7, Folder 319)
    - 1971 Sep (Box 7, Folder 320)
    - 1971 Oct (Box 7, Folder 321)
    - 1971 Nov (Box 7, Folder 322)
    - 1971 Dec (Box 7, Folder 323)
    - 1972 Jan (Box 7, Folder 324)
    - 1972 Feb (Box 7, Folder 325)
    - 1972 Apr (Box 7, Folder 326)
    - 1972 May (Box 7, Folder 327)
    - 1972 Oct (Box 7, Folder 328)
    - 1972 Nov (Box 7, Folder 329)
    - 1972 Dec (Box 7, Folder 330)
    - 1973 Jan (Box 7, Folder 331)
    - 1973 Feb (Box 7, Folder 332)
    - 1973 Sep (Box 7, Folder 333)
    - 1973 Oct (Box 7, Folder 334)
    - 1973 Nov (Box 7, Folder 335)
    - 1974 Sep (Box 7, Folder 336)
    - 1981 Sep (Box 7, Folder 337)
    - 1981 Oct (Box 7, Folder 338)
    - 1981 Nov (Box 7, Folder 339)
    - 1981 Dec (Box 7, Folder 340)
    - 1982 Jan (Box 7, Folder 341)
    - 1982 Feb (Box 7, Folder 342)
    - 1982 Mar (Box 7, Folder 343)
    - 1982 Apr (Box 7, Folder 344)
    - 1982 May (Box 7, Folder 345)
    - 1982 Jun-Aug (Box 7, Folder 346)
    - 1982 Sep (Box 7, Folder 347)
    - 1982 Oct (Box 7, Folder 348)
    - 1982 Nov (Box 7, Folder 349)
    - 1982 Dec (Box 7, Folder 350)
    - 1983 Jan (Box 7, Folder 351)
    - 1983 Feb (Box 7, Folder 352)
    - 1983 Mar (Box 7, Folder 353)
    - 1983 Apr (Box 7, Folder 354)
    - 1983 May (Box 7, Folder 355)
    - 1983 Jun-Aug (Box 7, Folder 356)
    - 1983 Sep (Box 7, Folder 357)
    - 1983 Oct (Box 7, Folder 358)
    - 1983 Nov (Box 7, Folder 359)
    - 1983 Dec (Box 7, Folder 360)
    - 1985 Feb (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - 1985 Mar (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - 1985 Apr (Box 8, Folder 363)
    - 1985 May (Box 8, Folder 364)
    - 1985 Jun - Aug (Box 8, Folder 365)
    - 1985 Sep (Box 8, Folder 366)
    - 1985 Oct (Box 8, Folder 367)
    - 1985 Nov (Box 8, Folder 368)
    - 1985 Dec (Box 8, Folder 369)
    - 1986 Jan (Box 8, Folder 370)
    - 1986 Feb (Box 8, Folder 371)
    - 1986 Mar (Box 8, Folder 372)
    - 1986 Apr (Box 8, Folder 373)
    - 1986 May (Box 8, Folder 374)
    - 1986 Jun (Box 8, Folder 375)
    - 1986 Aug (Box 8, Folder 376)
    - 1986 Oct (Box 8, Folder 377)
    - 1986 Nov (Box 8, Folder 378)
    - 1986 Dec (Box 8, Folder 379)
    - 2003 Jan (Box 8, Folder 380)
    - 2003 Feb (Box 8, Folder 381)
    - 2003 Mar (Box 8, Folder 382)
    - 2003 Apr (Box 8, Folder 383)
    - 2003 May (Box 8, Folder 384)
    - 2003 Jun (Box 8, Folder 385)
    - 2003 Jul (Box 8, Folder 386)
    - 2003 Aug (Box 8, Folder 387)
    - 2003 Sep (Box 8, Folder 388)
    - 2003 Oct (Box 8, Folder 389)
    - 2003 Nov (Box 8, Folder 390)
    - 2003 Dec (Box 8, Folder 391)
    - 2004 Jan (Box 9, Folder 392)
    - 2004 Feb (Box 9, Folder 393)
    - 2004 Mar (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - 2004 Apr (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - 2004 May (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - 2004 Jun (Box 9, Folder 397)
    - 2004 Jul (Box 9, Folder 398)
    - 2004 Aug (Box 9, Folder 399)
    - 2005 Jan (Box 9, Folder 400)
    - 2005 Feb (Box 9, Folder 401)
    - 2005 Mar (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - 2005 Apr (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - 2004 May (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - 2005 Jul (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - 2005 Aug (Box 9, Folder 406)
    - 2005 Sep (Box 9, Folder 407)
    - 2005 Oct (Box 9, Folder 408)
    - 2005 Nov (Box 9, Folder 409)
    - 2005 Dec (Box 9, Folder 410)
  - University Public Worship Notes
    - Lenten Booklet, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - Worship Notes, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 412)
    - Worship Notes, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 413)
    - Worship Notes, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 414)
    - Inserts for Worship Notes, 1999-2003 (Box 9, Folder 415)
  - Battell Newsletter
    - 2001 (Box 9, Folder 416 - 417)
    - 2002 Jan-Sep (Box 9, Folder 418 - 422)
    - 2002 Oct-Dec (Box 10, Folder 423 - 425)
    - 2004 (Box 10, Folder 426 - 437)
    - 2005 Jan-May (Box 10, Folder 438 - 442)
  - Special Bulletins and Remembrance Materials
    - Special Bulletins, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 443)
    - Special Bulletins, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 444)
    - Special Bulletins, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 445)
    - Memorial Bulletins, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 446)
    - Service of Rememberance, 1994-2000 (Box 10, Folder 447 - 448)
    - Memorial Services, 1976-1999 (Box 10, Folder 449 - 471)
    - Third Sunday Music (Box 11, Folder 472)
    - Service of Music, Silence and Light, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 473)
    - Church Membership Directory, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 474)
    - Newsletter, 2000 Spring (Box 11, Folder 475)
    - Newsletter, 1999 January (Box 11, Folder 476)
    - Newsletter, 1998 December (Box 11, Folder 477)
    - Newsletter, 1998 November (Box 11, Folder 478)
    - Newsletter, 1998 October (Box 11, Folder 479)
    - Newsletter, 1998 May (Box 11, Folder 480 - 481)
    - Newsletter, 1998 April (Box 11, Folder 482)
    - Newsletter, 1998 March (Box 11, Folder 483)
    - Newsletter, 1998 February (Box 11, Folder 484)
  - Booklets
    - Lenten, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 485)
    - Lent, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 486)
    - Lenten, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 487)
    - Lenten, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 488)
    - Lenten, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 489)
    - Welcome Cards, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 490)
    - Holy Week, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 491)
    - Church Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 492)
    - Adult Education Battell, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 493)
  - Services
    - News Clippings, 1994-2000 (Box 11, Folder 494)
- Battell Chapel bulletins, Accession 2013-A-014
  The materials are open for research.
  - Bulletins, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 1-9)